 <?xml version="1.0" encoding ="UTF-8"?>
 <blog>
   <posts>
	<post id="1">
		<date>April 22, 2023</date>
		<author>Christopher Ospina</author>
		<title>How will AI change the world</title>
		<summary>
			<image_path>https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/thumb/0/04/ChatGPT_logo.svg/1200px-ChatGPT_logo.svg.png</image_path>
			<text>How I think AI will change the world</text>
		</summary>
		<body>Aritifical Intelligence has always been part of our daily lives since the 1950s but now we are at the age where
		AI controls how we perform daily activites as a species such as exchanging money, voting for government officials, software development
		and even household chores. This may sound like something out of science fiction but it is happening right now in the present day.
		For example, we are using ChatGBT as an assistant to help us through technical issues. Meanwhile, Elon Musk has developed self-driving cars
		and the biochip which I predict will be mandated by 2040. There are also mechanical robots that are used for manufacturing. However there is a 
		dark side to AI. There have been reports of AI becoming self-aware so much that eventually they will revolt on humans and cause 
		major exctinction to our society. There have been movies about the matter such as Avengers: Age of Ultron and Terminator but if this were to
		be real it would lead to total disaster. 
		</body>
	</post>
	<post id="2">
		<date>April 23 2023</date>
		<author>Christopher Ospina</author>
		<title>My review of the Super Mario Movie</title>
		<summary>
			<image_path>https://hips.hearstapps.com/hmg-prod.s3.amazonaws.com/images/mario-and-luigi-the-super-mario-bros-movie-640adf6e1b728.jpg</image_path>
			<text>A review of the Super Mario Movie as I saw it last week</text>
		</summary>
		<body>The Super Mario Movie is so far as of yet the biggest animated film of 2023 and already it has
		surpassed Disney's Frozen II, but is it really for the hype or will it flop? Let's find out!
		The plot follows Mario and Luigi as they are transported from Brooklyn to the Mushroom Kingdom they learn
		from Princess Peach that Bowser itends to use the star to take over the Kingdom only because he has a crush on Peach
		Mario and Peach intend to use the Kongs for assistance. I really enjoy how they incorporate themes from the Super Mario series
		into the film's score and hidden references to other Mario media like the satruday morning cartoon and the 1993 live 
		action movie. I am anticipating a sequel or even a shared Nintendo universe leading to a Super Smash Bros Movie that incorporates Zelda
		and Pokemon. This is also part of a renaissance of animation from Universal Pictures that began with The Bad Guys and which included
		Minions: Rise of Gru and Puss in Boots: The Last Wish. They own Illumination Entertainment and Dreamworks Animation.
		A Super Mario sequel, a live action How To Train Your Dragon and Shrek 5 have been confirmed to be in the works. Also Epic Universe is under construction
		at Universal Studios Orlando with Mario themed attractions as well as those from How to Train Your Dragon and
		Fantastic Beasts. We all need a break from Disney's dominance and I think we are getting close to Universal
		stealing the spotlight.</body>
	</post>
	<post id="3">
		<date>April 24 2023</date>
		<author>Christopher Ospina</author>
		<title>Top 10 Disney World attractions</title>
		<summary>https
			<image_path>://encrypted-tbn0.gstatic.com/images?q=tbn:ANd9GcTbbitGAYVFzzZvhLmiSUEioiE8cZ8rCaZu_n6B2oiZXA</image_path>
			<text>A countdown of my Top 10 Disney World Attractions that I have been on</text>
		</summary>
		<body>
		The Disney theme parks are known for their attractions which amuse guests from all around the world. They could tell 
		an original story or be themed to an existing Disney IP or even third-party if applicable. In these rides it is important
		that they give guests the whole expierence of being part of the story that the ride is trying to tell. I have been lucky to
		visit Walt Disney World resort in the past two years and before to expierence these thrills. Here's a countdown of the Top 10
		attractions at Walt Disney World resort specifically Magic Kingdom, EPCOT and Disney's Hollywood Studios. 

		Note: Splash Mountain is currently closed due to racism issues with its source material and will be rethemed to
		Tiana's Bayou Adventure based on the 2009 film The Princess and The Frog.

		 10. Twilight Zone Tower of Terror (DHS)
		 9. Rock'n Roll Coaster Featuring Aerosmith (DHS)
		 8. The Haunted Mansion (Magic Kingdom)
		 7. Big Thunder Mountain Railroad (Magic Kingdom)
		 6. Toy Story Mania (DHS)
		 5. Pirates of the Caribbean (Magic Kingdom)
		 4. Soarin' (EPCOT)
		 3. Splash Mountain (Magic Kingdom)
		 2. Test Track (EPCOT)
		 1. Star Wars: Rise of the Resistance (DHS)
	    
		 Honorable Mentions:
		  1. Spaceship Earth (EPCOT)
		  2. Frozen Ever After (EPCOT)
		  3. Peter Pan's Flight (Magic Kingdom)
		  4. Seven Dwarfs Mine Train (Magic Kingdom)
		</body>
	</post>
	</posts>
</blog>